STEPHANIA NEVADO

Manager / Nutritionist

♦ Phone

+34666366475

□ Instagram

https://instagram.com/nutrinevado

nutrinevado@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/stephania nevado



Manager with a licentiate degree in nutrition and dietetics and 8 years of experience. Passionate about leadership, change management, process improvement and team work. Always curious to learn new things. Creator of Nutrinevado Nutrition and co-founder of Nutreto.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FOUNDER

Nutrinevado | Sep 2013 - Present

- Personalised nutrition advice.
- Online consultations

NATIONAL MANAGER OF NUTRITION & OBESITY

Vivanta Clinics | Aug 2020 - May 2021

- Protocol management,
- Management of a multidisciplinary team.
- Online and face-to-face bariatric surgery training.
- Management of agreements, collaboration contracts and rates.
- Control of invoices, expenses and orders for surgical material.

HEAD OF THE OBESITY DEPARTMENT

Diego de León Clinics | Jun 2016 - Aug 2020

- Leader of the overweight and obesity unit.
- Specialist in bariatric surgery patients.
- First-time face-to-face and online patient consultations.
- Nutritional monitoring in person and online.
- Recording of audiovisual material for social networks: explanatory videos for YouTube, Instagram, Facebook, Twitter, etc.

NUTRITIONIST & DIETIST CONSULTANT

Medsure Ocupacional | May 2014 - May 2015

- Nutritional consultations for all types of patients.
- Health days for company employees.

SUPERVISOR

Restoven de Venezuela C.A | Feb 2013 - Jun 2014

- Supervision of the food service of La Trinidad Teaching Medical Center Clinic.
- Supervision catering to companies (Bayer, HBO, Biotech, Colgate, etc.).
- Personal training in food handling.
- Management protocols.
- Menu preparation and therapeutic diet programming.

COURSES

- How to be a nutritional expert at ED 2020
- Your guide to know everything about your menstrual cycle 2020
- How to eat more plants in 6 simple steps 2020
- Introduction to the Meisner technique of action and direction 2015
- ⁻ The theatre game II 2013
- Safe handling of chemical products basic concepts, cleaning and sanitation - 2013
- The theatre game I 2013
- Eating psychology: ED childhood and adolescence 2012

EDUCATION

LICENTIATE DEGREE IN NUTRITION AND DIETETICS Faculty of Medicine, School of Nutrition and Dietetics

Central University of Venezuela | 2007 - 2013

- Coordinator of hospital and community internships.
- Community service in the autism unit.



CO-FOUNDER

Nutreto | Apr 2020 - Present

I wanted to try out creating a HealthTech product and get more hands-on experience by taking a digital product from idea to release. Nutreto is a cloud-based platform for nutrition and health, usable for both patients and clinics. Check it out at nutreto.com!

P SKILLS

- Team management
- Leadership
- Process and protocol planing
- Team work
- Personalized nutritional guidance

CONFERENCES

NUTRITION AND EXERCISE SCIENCE

Venezuelan Congress | Feb - Mar 2013

NEW TECHNOLOGIES AND INNOVATIONS IN THE PRODUCTION PROCESSES APPLIED TO FOOD

Feeding you | Nov 2011

60th ANNIVERSARY OF THE SCHOOL OF NUTRITION AND DIETETICS

Venezuelan Congress | Nov 2010

LANGUAGES	
Spanish (native)	
English (intermediate)	
Swedish (beginner)	